ah boop-she do a dory should be do a
dude she do pidor Ibuki boop de doop
oh no de Buci doopy doopy dory more
doors for me
pesky bird a Dory deep lots of doors for
me
a door for me label these more doors for
me Oh Deary me another door for me it'll
do for me a couple of dory deeds hello
and I have got myself lots and lots of
doors fulfilling my challenge from
mumbo-jumbo but we need to head back to
our base now that we have got some doors
I must admit I've been collecting doors
for 20 minutes now and this is the worst
nether hub I've ever seen I could not
find my way around at all there are some
people that didn't get hit I did get
quite a few doors today we got tangos
false beef beef beef Corrales zeref's
and we got some Exuma as well so another
quick collection they have no idea of
course and we shall head back to our
base some people haven't even bothered
replacing their front door honestly
they've just left it there and I need to
check on my neighbors cuz these guys
have been replacing their doors some
people don't even have front doors so
they got off lightly but most of them do
trap door trap see trap door just isn't
hello trap door isn't the same so it's
got to be a front door but I tell you
who does always always replace their
front door is good times with scar and
he has not disappointed good times with
scar gives me another spruce door thanks
scar right let's get back into it now
that we've stolen some doors so last
episode we started working on this and
it looks like scar has decorated this
one which actually looks really really
cool he's given it some texture and I
think probably he's he's only done one
is even a half a job he's done a quarter
of a job so hopefully that will get all
decorated up and yeah I think this is
gonna look really cool let's go and put
these doors or
way for a second because I need to hide
them I don't know what I'm gonna do with
all these doors but I Oh blimey oh yeah
I forgot I forgot mum I must have sent
me a message
I took some cactus he took some cactus
oh yeah he did take some cactus this I
think this was completely full I don't
know why on earth you would need that
much of did he mean green dye or cactus
cuz I don't actually have cactus that's
fine
mean me and mumbo have a a an
understanding okay we have an
understanding but if I can borrow if I
can borrow his stuff he can borrow mine
and then I can oh oh my I heard it I
heard it oh no oh no I heard let me go
off it I just did I just didn't click no
way
no let's go let's go no I gotta get the
tag back he's gone for the tie is he
gone for the tag my windows no no you
did it hello well it's easy he's got it
oh yeah using mumbos messaging system oh
my goodness you'll help me I don't think
I want your help I don't think I don't
think I want my I don't think I need
your help
it's oh my goodness ah I I don't believe
this
that was really clever I had absolutely
no idea oh no all my doors
hold on those are my pumpkin pies no no
no no no no no no but the bounty of war
I don't I don't really know what to do
with myself I don't know what to do
myself
he's just out oh he's rubbing it in my
face now I have 15 points you have to
hold on to that for 15 hours to be ahead
of me don't worry a scout I'll get it
back I just I feel so betrayed I feel so
betrayed I thought I thought that mumbo
I thought the mumbo said
me a message did mom believe it did did
mum Mambo Mambo even send that message
no I think the worst thing is that Mambo
is not messaging me well played well
played look at this look at the observer
track that he's got going up there I
can't I just I just I I have mixed
emotions I'm I'm impressed
I I feel betrayed and most of all I'm
disappointed that that message wasn't
even from I was so excited I've been
sending Mambo message every day just
like hi Mambo how are you and then just
I get nothing
are you nothing back and then I think
this that's really if I would have a
message system that I could send you
messages I'd send your daily messages
you didn't lose any items right no I'm
so lost no no no no no damage done
no damage no don't damage I'm surprised
like how many TNT was that it was just
one it was just one drop that the very
heard if I heard it just as I destroyed
it was like and like you know the
Pistons sound right that was i almost
rehearse it so I heard that Shh and then
I heard in my brain as well another no
well I've been sad here for like two
hours in your little smelt room I even
made a chair in here I was I was really
bored yeah I made a chair I was sitting
here 15 hours 15 hours with the tag it
was actually surprisingly little damage
now yeah this is this is exactly what
you expect from a game like this to be
fair well done I have to I have to take
a little bow shed a little chair say say
goodbye to this for now I can't believe
you rubbed it in my face as well thank
you you win oh I shall leave now I'm
still a little bit shook to be honest it
was only a matter of time
I'm that someone was gonna get the tag
from me that was really clever that was
really really clever way of getting me I
don't even quite remember how it was in
here to be honest with you that's the
problem sometimes with with builds like
this like I just kind of made it on the
fly I don't actually remember exactly
how it went so I've just got to accept
tag is not with me for now do you know
what I'm a little bit relieved just a
little bit because I was getting a bit
paranoid seriously I've been building
away at my base and I've just been
looking over my shoulder every second
paranoid that someone's coming to get me
so I think I think I'm quite happy to
let go of the tag just for a little
while but I'll get it back in the end
we've still got 15 points which is to be
fair since I'm the first person I don't
know if that's a lot but it's definitely
a good place to start either way my
heart's still going a little bit I'm
still I'm still I still haven't quite
processed what has had just happened I
just I feel just so I'm so betrayed
would it kill you to send me a message
once in a while mumbo just what anyway
what I think we should do is continue
with this build I have been itching and
raring to go to keep making some
progress on my mansion build I have
obviously been working away at this and
I have got it mostly planned out already
so it's just the case of recreating it
here in all of its glory so let's get
into another time-lapse get this thing
with some progress we've got a we're
gonna grind this out
[Music]
again I've had to stop myself and the
time lapse from completing this build
far too quickly as you can see I have
been making really really good progress
and you know what it's not even the
resources that are limiting me at this
point it is actually time I have spent
many hours building this thing and I'm
gonna have to pace myself otherwise I
won't be able to upload a video for
another week either way I think this is
going absolutely wonderfully take a look
at that you can really see where this is
going I'm not gonna spoil the full build
just yet but you can see where this is
going and I think next episode I will be
able to complete the whole thing well
the front it's very much only a pretty
face at the moment because round the
back it's actually nothing there is
there is no back whatsoever but I have
had a little wonder on the inside and I
do think there will be enough space here
for everything I'm going to need but on
the whole it's looking it's looking
pretty decent well maybe not this side
now in order to complete some of these
things I needed a lot of anvils now I
don't know how many of you play
Minecraft frequently but each anvil
costs a lot of iron and I didn't have a
lot of iron so I messaged mumbo and he
kindly allowed me to use his iron farm
so I had been afk over there for quite
some time here to be exact this is where
mumbos iron farm is and he kindly
offered me to use it so I could get the
anvils that I required
so what I did hello hello hello what I
did was quite hello what I did was I
actually a fk'd here a lot longer than I
needed to fill up some of these chests
for him so not only did it not cost him
anything he's made a bunch more iron
than I used just because iaf Kade here
for a really long time but even though
I've given him lots of iron through my
afk I'm actually gonna send him a couple
of diamonds in the messaging system I'm
pretty sure this won't blow up again
okay good yeah I think the bail system
doesn't work anymore
might need to fix that up there we go a
couple of diamonds thanks for letting me
use your farm I love this thing off you
go now even though I've already placed
as you can see lots of cauldrons and
lots of anvils I'm actually going to
need a lot more than the ones that I've
got here so it would be a really good
idea for me to get a steady trickle of
ironing so don't want to have to use
mumbos hard work all the time I mean it
was yeah it was nice that IFK knows it
was great for what I needed to get done
here but I've actually accidentally
created an iron farm already and I was
wondering maybe there's something I can
do here just to harvest these golems
without having to get myself killed
every time yeah I'm looking at you so
I'm wondering if I can retrofit this
obviously it's not going to be efficient
at all but I accidentally created this
golem farm so I'm sure with a bit of
engineering I can get these guys to do
what I want them to and I'm thinking it
might be as simple as getting them to
agro onto a mob of some kind
fold out a hole and well into into a
collection system of some kind this
should be really simple
in theory in theory and in practice it
might be entirely different and it might
not work at all but just a steady
trickle of iron would be really great I
think it's as simple as this a
collection system here into a chest and
then I think just some signs and a lava
so I've just got to get them to go in
this hole and well perish unfortunately
add all the signs add the lava ok let's
think about this sensibly there we go
now let's see let's see if this works
let's just push this guy in before we go
any further go on in you go in you go
there we go there we go there we go
simple as that okay that worked that was
a really easy retrofit now we just got
to get them to go inside you know I
could actually foresee some danger there
so I'm gonna remove that until I've got
everything in place
the Sun is going down and all I got to
do is wait for a zombie to appear oh
cool
get out of here there we go hello zombie
yep yep yep come with me we're going for
a little ride
you and I well oh goodness gracious me
tell you what I might be able to time
this right cuz I need one of them to
have a mob head on them and missed
missed missed I'm fed up of these there
we go
honestly absent or an absolute nightmare
and can we put the hat on now there we
go right okay brilliant you are exactly
where we needed you to be okay yes sleep
sleep sleep this fella should be safe
from the Sun now alright let's see if we
can get this guy all the way over here
Ernie's off up he goes I hope this works
come on and all the way up to the top
yeah success success but actually that
went well for once now I actually have
no idea if a iron golem is gonna agro on
this guy at all so this is very much an
experiment so let's just sly it
let's just silence this guy hopefully he
should stop talking hey hey don't look
at me like that
oh wait no it didn't maybe I did
something wrong I thought that was that
was meant to shut him up now I didn't
want to put him too low that the iron
golems cuz they have a big reach you see
and I was kind of hoping that they were
just aggro to him there but I may need
to lower him and that's why I put him so
high up we'll have to test when an iron
golem comes in but I think for
retrofitting this thing just a zombie
sitting in a minecart I mean it looks
hilarious by the way I could even do
something a little bit more
effective here and by that I mean making
it look a little bit less like there's
just a random floating zombie just make
a quick crane to make it seem at least
like this guy's not just floating well
it doesn't look amazing but it will do
for now
it's just to see if this works and that
this guy's just not randomly floating so
now that we've got our inexpensive iron
farm being tested there's actually
something else I wanted to do you'll
notice that I've got 91 levels and I've
actually thought of something genius
it's stupid but genius you're about to
understand what I mean I don't
understand this myself but here's the
thing what I'm about to do is both
genius and incredibly stupid at the same
time it melts my brain but what we're
gonna do is we're gonna collect our own
minecraft mob head and I've been
wondering to myself for a while how do
you PvP yourself well we're about to see
if it works but I actually have 91
levels as you can see down the bottom
there and there's no point ending my
Minecraft life if I'm gonna lose all
those levels so what I'm gonna do is
actually actually do a deuce car a favor
because he has got kikiki
cocooned what does this mean cocooned
key good mmm
I don't know any of this stuff even
means anyway he's got a box of alight
rehearse so what I'm gonna do is I'm
gonna take this and I'm gonna use my 91
levels to enchant these four scars so
that he doesn't have to mud as well
instead of just losing them oh okay okay
cool so you're gonna spawn in here but
not up there you know what you can you
can sit here and you can watch
unbreaking books there we go okay I
don't have nearly enough emeralds for
this so we're only gonna ensure a few of
these election then bending and breaking
I seem to be missing a bunch of doors
anything no anyway
anyone know anything about that my my
door is missing too there we go so
that's a pretty good deed there I've
done a lot of enchanting that's a huge
amount of books if he had to purchase
these four diamonds oh my goodness
gracious me okay so we'll pop this back
in scars base cuz we're now at 32 levels
which is a much more normal and
respectable amount of levels good guy
green doing some work okay so now we can
do what I was actually planning to
remember we were getting rid of our
levels so that we can try and collect
our own head maybe some of you have
worked out what I'm about to do maybe
some of you haven't but if this works we
may be able to break the system and I
can't see why not
I can't see why this wouldn't work okay
here we go
[Laughter]
caching alright so we need we need three
of these and then we can submit our own
head oh this is brilliant move okay
there's two green heads people in the
chat so confused
okay Green three green Nets killed by
green and now we can go back to our
daily lives I still don't think we have
much of a chance of winning this head
game but if we could do things like that
my goodness we might we might be able to
keep up a little bit where am I
there we go green so false managed to
get my head here somehow but I can get
those two and then this one really
absolutely brilliant I should also when
it's double green day I will submit all
of them and get double points for that
oh my goodness that was that that is
good that is he that was smart this is
what I mean
the smartest and dumbest thing you could
possibly do catching your own arrows I'm
still in fifth with 124 yeah
it's unlikely I'm gonna catch up anytime
soon but with a grain sorry grain you
think you think I'm bread tell you don't
who this great I live I'm not even on
the leaderboard there's this British
grain character is now I know that
there's already a rocket shop on the
server there's one already at the
shopping district Matt but in terms of
things that we can sell from our farms
I'm I don't have an iron farm and I've
spent everything on this base but what
we do have is a lot of gunpowder and a
lot of sugarcane so I think what we
could do is the first bit of real
competition on the server scar and I
might if I can convince him partner up
to get a brand new rocket shop on the
server so our message scar and see if
he's up for that I just need I just need
one iron golem to spawn seriously why if
why are they not spawning anymore you
guys need more bread you want some bread
you want some bread from this grain
character goods have given us more bread
we must show to Boyd I've been waiting
here for so long and the only iron golem
that spawned is in there
absolutely I've given up I've got iron
blocks we're just gonna spawn one in and
see what happens because he may not go
for this guy at all but there's only one
way to fight oh I got an achievement
oh no he's interested now he's
interested he sees him he see he's like
oh oh you could you you come down here
you come down here
but it's he's not walking in on his own
now that's that's actually quite
annoying cuz I thought I thought he
would I thought we would I thought we
would just go for it he's not even
moving either he's not moving at all
just push him in I think it's cuz he's
my own golem I don't know if he's gonna
act differently but he definitely sees
him he's just not going I won't I won't
get my investment back on that guy
but anyway now looks like it might be a
slight failure but I'm gonna tinker with
it I'm gonna tinker with it see if we
can get this to work a little bit better
than it currently does and we'll see
what happens from there but I'm afraid
that is all we have time for today as
always we've made some pretty good
progress we have got ourselves a
non-functional that can be improved iron
trickle farm and we've made lots of
progress on the base and we've submitted
a bunch of heads for the game so that is
it for me everyone thank you very much
for watching I'll see you in the next
episode good